duplicitymovie.net 2013-03-25

# Universal Studios Entertainment Portal

This Privacy Policy was last updated on 05/03/2010.   

**Introduction:** Universal Studios Home Entertainment LLC ("USHE"), its parent, subsidiary and affiliated companies (collectively, "NBC Universal" or "we" or "our" or "us") maintain www.universalstudiosentertainment.com (the "Site") for your personal entertainment, information, education, and communication, and for additional marketing and customer service purposes. Your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Policy describes the types of information collected from you, what we do with it, with whom we share it, and how you can correct or change such information. It is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy carefully, especially before providing any personal data through the Site. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the Site, or other related concerns, please [contact us](http://www.universalstudios.com/contact_form.php?email_id=10). If you wish to unsubscribe from the Site, marketing, or the features or offerings for which you have previously registered, please visit the account management section of your Site account ("Account") or [contact us](http://www.universalstudios.com/contact_form.php?email_id=10).

**PLEASE REVIEW THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THE TERMS OF USE FOR THE SITE CAREFULLY. YOUR USE OF THE SITE SIGNIFIES THAT YOU CONSENT TO THE COLLECTION, USE AND STORAGE OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA, IP ADDRESS, AND AGGREGATE AND ANONYMOUS DATA IN THE UNITED STATES IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AND THAT YOU AGREE TO[THE TERMS OF USE](http://www.universalstudiosentertainment.com/about/terms-of-use.php) **.

1\. Types of Information Collected  
    · Personal Data  
    · IP Addresses  
    · Aggregate and Anonymous Data

2\. Use of Cookies and Other Technologies

3\. Our Use of Your Data  
    · Personal Data  
    · IP Addresses  
    · AA Data

4\. Disclosure of Personal Data to Third Parties  
    · Disclosure to Affiliates  
    · Disclosure to Third Parties  
    · Disclosure to Others

5\. Third Party Advertising and Partnerships With Other Sites

6\. Your Choices

7\. Access and Correction

8\. Children and Privacy  
   · Children Under the Age of 13  
   · Children Between the Ages of 13 and 18 

9\. Data Security Disclaimer

10\. Exclusions

11\. Other Terms and Conditions

12\. Applicable Law

13\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

14\. Contacting Us Regarding Your Privacy

______________________________________________________________________ 

1\. Types of Information Collected:

**Personal Data:** Personally identifiable information ("Personal Data") is any information that can be used to identify a specific individual, such as your name, email address, home address, phone number and credit card information. The Site collects Personal Data when you interact with it: for example when you subscribe for newsletters; submit postings; register for membership services such as chat rooms or message boards; respond to polls or surveys; purchase merchandise; register for sweepstakes, contests and other promotional opportunities; or seek help from our customer service departments. We also may collect information when you purchase products or services offline. Because providing detailed information regarding our privacy policy when you register or providing information in connection with these other services often proves impractical, you may instead be provided with a short notice that reminds you to refer to this Privacy Policy and other relevant information from us. We may also obtain Personal Data from reputable third parties, such as credit agencies. 

**IP Addresses:** When you visit the Site, we collect your IP address. An IP address is associated with the access point through which you enter the Internet, and is typically controlled by your Internet Service Provider (ISP), your company, or your university. We may use IP addresses to collect information regarding the frequency with which users visit various parts of the Site. Standing alone, your IP address may or may not be personally identifiable. We do not knowingly link IP addresses to Personal Data.

**Aggregate and Anonymous Data:** Aggregate and anonymous data is information that does not identify you, specifically including data collected automatically through the operation of the Site ("AA Data"). For example, we may collect Site usage data in the aggregate (such as which Site features you visit and in what sequence) through the use of various technologies as further described in paragraph 2 below. We may also collect password information from you when you log in, and aggregate computer and connection information; and during some visits, we may use software tools to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, time spent on certain pages and page interaction information. We will use such AA Data only in AA Data form.

**2\. Use of Cookies and Similar Technologies:** Like many websites, we use "cookies" or other similar technologies to collect AA Data. A cookie is a small data file that is saved in the persistent storage on your computer's hard drive for record keeping purposes when you visit the Site. Cookies allow us to measure traffic activity on the Site and to improve your user experience, for example by remembering your passwords and viewing preferences, allowing you to visit "member only" or age-appropriate portions of the Site without re-registering, and tracking the progress and number of entries in activities that require registration or entry, such as sweepstakes. Similarly, if you have asked us to send you information about upcoming products and promotions, using cookies, we collect information about which Site pages you have visited and in what order ("Clickstream Data") that may allow us to narrow or limit the materials provided to you based on your preset preferences. Computers are initially set to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can set your computer to refuse cookies, but it is likely that some parts, if not all, of the Site will not function properly if you do so.

**3\. Our Use of Your Data:**

**Personal Data:** We will use your Personal Data for the purposes for which it was provided. For example, if you provide Personal Data to register for a newsletter or a text messaging service, to enter a contest or a sweepstake, or to purchase goods or services, we will use it to register you for or provide you with those goods or services. When you provide us with your Personal Data for this purpose, we may ask you whether you wish to receive information about features, services and other offerings that may be of interest to you. We also may send information or offers to selected groups of users on behalf of other businesses. When we do this, we do not give those businesses your name or address without your permission. Under certain circumstances (for example, if you win a contest) we may post your Personal Data on the Site. We will notify you of this possibility when you provide the Personal Data and, if possible, when the Personal Data is posted. We may also use your Personal Data to notify you about important changes to the Site. 

Cookies and similar tools may be used to relate your use of the Site and AA Data to Personal Data obtained from you. If any AA Data is linked with Personal Data, the linked AA Data will then be treated as Personal Data.

**IP Addresses:** IP addresses are used for the purposes of system administration. We may also use IP addresses to provide AA Data to advertisers about the volume of use on the Site, and as further set forth herein.

**AA Data:** We may also use Personal Data and IP addresses in aggregate form for purposes of research or analysis. In order to better understand and serve the users of the Site, we (possibly in conjunction with a third party) often conduct research on customer demographics, interests and behavior based on Personal Data and IP addresses we gather. Although this aggregated data may be based in part on Personal Data, it does not identify you personally. We may share this type of AA Data with a variety of third parties, including its affiliates, agents, and current and prospective business partners.

We may use AA Data collected from the Site for administration, advertising and promotional purposes, and we may share such information with various affiliated and unaffiliated entities for such purposes. For example, Clickstream Data and demographic AA Data may be shared with our advertisers and business partners. We may also enter into agreements with outside companies that possess technology that allows the Site to customize the advertising and marketing messages you receive on the Site or through email. This data (including Clickstream Data about your activities on the Site) may be shared with these companies for this purpose.

**4\. Disclosure of Your Data:**

**Disclosure to Affiliates:** We reserve the right to share Personal Data with our affiliates, including our parent company and its subsidiaries. If you do not want us to share your Personal Data with our affiliated companies for their marketing purposes, you may opt-out of such sharing at any time by visiting the account management section of your Account or by [contacting us](http://www.universalstudios.com/contact_form.php?email_id=10).

**Disclosure to Third Parties:** Like many businesses, we sometimes hire third parties to perform certain business-related functions on our behalf such as hosting specific portions of the Site, maintaining databases, delivering content, sending marketing emails, administering contests, mailing information, processing payments, or otherwise operating the Site (singularly "Third Party" or collectively, "Third Parties"). When we employ a Third Party to perform these functions, that Third Party will only be provided with the particular Personal Data, IP addresses and/or AA Data it needs to perform its function, and is required to protect such Personal Data, IP addresses and/or AA Data. With your consent, we may also share Personal Data with pre-screened third parties for their marketing or promotional purposes. We will provide you with an opportunity to elect or decline these services or opportunities (see "Your Choices" below). In the event you have elected to "unsubscribe" from any of our services, we will share your Personal Data with third parties with whom we jointly offer such services solely to the extent necessary to ensure that your request not to receive such communications is honored. In addition, for third-party sponsored sweepstakes, contests or promotions, we may request Personal Data from you that may be shared with the sponsor upon their request, but we will give you the option to either agree to this use of your Personal Data or cancel your participation in the applicable sweepstakes, contest, or promotion at the time we request such Personal Data.

**Disclosure to Others:** In addition, we may disclose Personal Data and IP addresses without providing you with a choice under the following limited circumstances to: (1) protect the legal rights, privacy or safety of NBC Universal, or its subsidiaries, affiliates or its or their employees, agents and contractors; (2) protect the safety and security of visitors to the Site or other properties; (3) protect against fraud or other illegal activity or for risk management purposes; (4) respond to inquiries or requests from public authorities; (5) permit us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain; (6) enforce our Terms of Use; or (7) comply with the law or legal process.

If we sell all or part of the Site or make a sale or transfer of assets or are otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, we may, in our sole discretion, transfer, sell or assign your Personal Data, IP address information, and/or AA Data to a third party as part of or in connection with that transaction. Upon such transfer, the Privacy Policy of the acquiring entity may govern the further use of your Personal Data, IP address information, and/or AA Data.

**5\. Third-Party Advertising and Partnerships with Other Sites:**

The Site may include third-party advertising. These third parties' online services, websites and advertisers, or the Internet advertising companies that work on their behalf, may use technology to send (or "serve") the advertisements that appear on the Site directly to your computer. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use certain technologies to deliver advertisements, collect information about the effectiveness of their advertisements, and to collect anonymous information about your visits to the Site, such as the number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other Personal Data). For more information about these specialized technologies, and how to "opt out" of information collection by these companies, we suggest you visit the privacy policies and terms of use/service for these companies.

Please note that the Site may provide access to other partner experiences that will not follow the same Privacy Policy as the Site. For instance, selecting an interface or other elements on the Site may take you to an entirely different online service controlled and operated by another company. These other services may use one of our logos or sub-brands as a result of a co-branding agreement. These services may use their own methods of collecting data, including Personal Data, and may make use of that data in ways that the Site would not. This Privacy Policy will not apply to Personal Data or any other data collected from or provided by you in connection with such partner experiences or partner services. You should check the partner's applicable privacy policy to determine how that partner will handle such data.

**6\. Your Choices:**

You can use the certain features of the Site without providing any Personal Data, but if you decline to provide Personal Data, you may not be able to use certain services or features. If you have previously provided Personal Data to the Site and have subscribed to one or more email newsletters or are receiving emails or other communications from us and you do not want to receive such emails, please discontinue your subscriptions by selecting the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of any message (if available), visiting the account management section of your Account, or by [contacting us](http://www.universalstudios.com/contact_form.php?email_id=10). You may opt-out of receiving offers from us and related products and services offered by third parties by adjusting your preferences in the account management section of your Account, or by c[contacting us](http://www.universalstudios.com/contact_form.php?email_id=10). If you ask that we stop using your Personal Data, we will honor that request; provided, that as stated above, you may not be able to continue using certain features of the Site that require Personal Data; and provided further, that we will retain records of your Personal Data as needed in order to comply with applicable federal, state, or local law.

**7\. Access and Correction:**

If you would like to review, correct or change the Personal Data that you have previously provided us, please visit the account management section of your Account, or [contact us](http://www.universalstudios.com/contact_form.php?email_id=10). We will take reasonable steps to update or correct Personal Data in our possession. 

**8\. Children and Privacy:**

We encourage parents and legal guardians to spend time with their age-appropriate children using the Site and to be fully familiar with the Site features that may be used by their children. We do not require a child to disclose more information than is reasonably necessary to participate in a contest, game or other activity or feature of the Site as a condition of participation. At various places on the Site, we may ask users for their age. By using or logging into the Site or related features or services, you agree to respond truthfully and accurately about your age.

**Children Under the Age of 13:**

**The Site is not directed to children under the age of 13. We will not knowingly collect or use Personal Data from anyone under 13 years of age. Children under the age of 13 years of age are expressly prohibited from submitting or posting any Personal Data on the Site.**

**Children Between the Ages of 13 and 18:**

**If you are between the ages of 13 and 18, please be sure to read this Privacy Policy with your parent and obtain his or her permission before you submit or post any Personal Data on the Site, and before you use any features or offerings of the Site.** Do not post your real name on the Site, in a chat room, or in any other feature of the Site, and never tell anyone online anything private about yourself or your family, including your phone number and address. Use screen names at all times. If you win a sweepstakes that has a prize, your parent will have to mail or fax us a signed note at the address or fax number listed in the rules for the specific contest that says it was OK for you to enter, and tells us they will accept the prize for you. Some areas of the Site may have special rules for children under the age of 18. When you are in those areas, you must follow those rules.

Parents and legal guardians may request a review and/or removal of their child's Personal Data at any time by [contacting us](http://www.universalstudios.com/contact_form.php?email_id=10), which must include the same screen name, password, and e-mail address that their child submitted. To protect the child's privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify the parent's or legal guardian's identity before granting him or her access to the child's Personal Data. 

**9\. Data Security Disclaimer:**

We take reasonable security precautions to secure the Personal Data that you choose to provide against the loss, misuse, alteration or unauthorized access of such information. Unfortunately, no transmission of data over the Internet is guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third parties not under our control to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. While we strive to protect your Personal Data, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any Personal Data you transmit to us. Any such transmission is done at your own risk. If you believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure, please notify us of the problem by [contacting us](http://www.universalstudios.com/contact_form.php?email_id=10).

**10\. Exclusions:**

This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to us on or through the Site ("Unsolicited Submissions"). Please see our [TERMS OF USE](http://www.universalstudiosentertainment.com/about/terms-of-use.php) for our policies regarding such Unsolicited Submissions. All such Unsolicited Submissions shall be deemed to be non-confidential, and USHE shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose and distribute such Unsolicited Submissions to others without limitation or attribution.

**11\. Other Terms and Conditions:**

Your access to and use of the Site is subject to [THE TERMS OF USE](http://www.universalstudiosentertainment.com/about/terms-of-use.php) . The terms of this Privacy Policy are incorporated into [THE TERMS OF USE](http://www.universalstudiosentertainment.com/about/terms-of-use.php) .

**12\. Applicable Law:**

We may engage one or more Third Parties to control and operate the Site in the United States. The Site is not intended to subject us to the laws or jurisdiction of any state, country or territory other than that of the United States, and the privacy and/or data protection laws of your own country may not apply to Personal Data collected by us. Please note that we do not represent or warrant that the Site is appropriate for use in any particular jurisdiction. 

**13\. Changes to this Privacy Policy:**

From time to time, we may revise this Privacy Policy to reflect industry initiatives, changes in the law or technology, or changes in our practices regarding information collection and use. If we make revisions to the way we collect or use Personal Data, we will post the amended Privacy Policy on the Site. Such modifications and updates shall be effective as of the date we post an amended Privacy Policy reflecting such changes on the Site. By logging into the Site or continuing to any feature or offering of the Site following such changes, you will be deemed to have agreed to such changes. You can determine when this Privacy Policy was last revised by referring to the "Last Updated" legend at the top of this page. We encourage you to check this Privacy Policy often for updates. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, as it may be amended from time to time, in whole or in part, do not continue using the Site or any feature or offering thereof.

**14\. Contacting Us Regarding Your Privacy:**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of NBC Universal who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, or if you have any other questions or requests as previously mentioned in this Privacy Policy, please write to us [here](http://www.universalstudios.com/contact_form.php?email_id=10) or at the address listed below: 

NBC UNIVERSAL FEEDBACK  
100 Universal City Plaza  
Bldg. 1360, 2nd Floor,  
Universal City, CA 91608
